

Isler Heiri Full Stack Engineer

With 10+ years of software development experience, I have contributed to projects small and large, demonstrating my professionalism with unmatched quality and reliability. Being a professional developer means understanding all the requirements of a project and finding the best way to implement it to a high-quality standard. As a senior full-stack engineer, I am proficient with modern web languages and I always focus on project structures and coding style, and etc. Also I have great experience with cloud architect and when it comes to AWS and GCP, I'm considering myself one of the most qualified engineers.

I am always ready to interview.

- mail: heiriis | er830@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/isler-heiri-24ba47238
- Phone: +1786 648 0527
- Github: https://github.com/crazycoder613

Projects



Cloud computing web-portal and Dashboard

Genesis Cloud offers cloud computing at unbeatable cost efficiency.

https://www.genesiscloud.com/



Django backend

Create or quote a translation job from a variety of services. The backend is capable of sending and receiving assets to an external Translation Management System which handles the actual translation.

https://orders.lionbridge.com/



Angular.Js, Vue.JS, Bootstrap, C3.js for Frontend and PHP Laravel 5.2 for Backend and Node.Js for Live Events.

Appointment Booking System for barbering.

https://www.capellis.com



ASP.NET + MSSQL

Forex rebates are a portion of the transaction cost that is paid back to the client on each trade, resulting in a lower spread and improved win ratio.

https://www.cashbackforex.com/

React Native + Firebase +Realm

Runa: Offers different ways to work with the Runes-messages, journaling.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? gl=US&hl=en_US&id=com.cloud9.runapp

React.js + GraphQL + Figma

Manage all your income in one place. Secure the bag, track your income. Visualize your grow using our interactive chart and view trends over time.



https://apps.apple.com/us/app/runa-runereading-your-life/id1503464150



Unity game



https://born-sniperassassin.en.uptodown.com/android/do wnload



Auto bot in MMORPG

Auto repeat **dungeon** rush including daily **dungeon**, group **dungeon**, and trial arena

tech stack used: Assembly, IDA, C++

https://www.bladeandsoul.com



Ionic + Typescript Mobile App

The app supports touch/face ID, QR scan, geolocation, camera and video capabilities and uses RESTful API on the server side.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.mobile.boss811



Spring Boot

Book flights online to worldwide destinations and enjoy a pleasant travel experience in comfort and safety. Look out for great offers and discounts.

https://www.lufthansa.com



Android, Swift Native App

Financial app: how much money you have on your balance or credit card with some charts at the bottom of the screen.



Stock Monitoring Application

Monitoring real time statistics application using MFC, Android, IOS Native

Skills

Programming Language:

C++(12 years), HTML(10), CSS(9), C#(8), JavaScript(7), TypeScript(6), PHP(6), Java(5), Swift(5), Asm(4), Python(2), Rust(1), Go(1), Solidity(1), GraphQL(2)

Platform, Framework, Library:

MFC(10 years), Unity(7), Java Spring Boot (5), React.js(6), Node.js(5), Next.js(2), Nest.js(2), Angular.js(5), Vue.js(4) Ionic(3), <u>ASP.NET(3)</u>, Laravel(4), Codelgniter(3), Django(2), Express.js(5), web3.js(1), Tailwind CSS(3), Bootstrap(6), Material UI(3), Ant Design (3)

Database Management System:

MySQL(8 years), MongoDB(5), MSSQL(8), SQLite(5), PostgreSQL(3), Realm(2),

Cloud Computing: AWS, GCP, Azure

Project management: Git, GitHub, Docker, Azura DevOps, Kubernetes

Testing framework: JEST, PHPUnit, JUnit, PyTest

Operating System: Windows, Android, Linux, Mac OS

Work Experience



Self-Employed Engineer

September 2021 - Present

- Maintain Cashback Forex website using ASP.NET+MSSQL(https://www.cashbackforex.com)
- -Built VoiceBrain website using React+Firebase (https://www.voicebrain.ai/)



Senior Full Stack Engineer

Fermat Software Remote September 2020 - August 2021

- Built online attendance management system with facial recognition
- MERN stack , React Native for frontend, PHP Laravel, Node, Django for backend Scrum Agile methodology for organizing efforts
- Developed Admin Panel using Laravel and Bootstrap 5, MYSQL



Lead Backend Engineer

Juix Remote January 2019 - August 2020

- Built REST apis for consumer services
- Built cloud infrastructure and integrated serverless architecture
- Implemented performance optimization for big queries



Senior Frontend Engineer

Proto Remote January 2018 - January 2019

- Built the drawing platforms by using the combination between HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React Native, Angular.js, Vue.js, Redux, TypeScript, Next.js, Material UI, Tailwind
- Deployed the app by using AWS VPC/ELB/RDS/ECS/S3/Cloud Front infrastructure.



Freelancer.com

Senior Mobile Developer January 2016 - January 2018

- Developed Android, IOS Native apps, Unity games and uploaded to Google Play store and App store.
- Developed hybrid app using Ionic framework and Node.js Socket.io Express.js, Python.
- Developed Auto Bots in the MMORPG games (Mu Origin, Black &Soul, PUBG) using debugging skills.



Senior Full Stack Engineer

Cliently January 2015 - January 2016

- implemented chrome extension for automated lead generation based on scraping
- implemented some 3rd party apis like MWS and Liveswitch (Webrtc)
- built some useful modules for various CRM functionalities

Education



University of Toronto

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2006 - 2010